{
  "sections": {
    "main": {
      "type": "main-product",
      "blocks": {
        "title": {
          "type": "title",
          "settings": {
            "display_on_card": false,
            "text_align": "text-left"
          }
        },
        "price": {
          "type": "price",
          "settings": {
            "display_on_card": false,
            "show_on_sale_sticker": false,
            "text_align": "text-left"
          }
        },
        "quantity_selector": {
          "type": "quantity_selector",
          "settings": {
            "display_on_card": false,
            "show_label": true
          }
        },
        "variant_picker": {
          "type": "variant_picker",
          "settings": {
            "display_on_card": false,
            "option_style": "buttons",
            "hide_option_labels": false,
            "enable_color_swatches": false
          }
        },
        "baf3083e-d14d-435d-bca3-100d6ac490ce": {
          "type": "buy_buttons",
          "settings": {
            "display_on_card": false,
            "show_price": true,
            "enable_payment_button": true,
            "show_pickup_availability": false
          }
        },
        "a17e90c4-acc9-4f1d-af84-828ae4cb2289": {
          "type": "description",
          "settings": {
            "display_on_card": false,
            "truncate_description": false,
            "text_align": "text-left"
          }
        }
      },
      "block_order": [
        "title",
        "price",
        "quantity_selector",
        "variant_picker",
        "baf3083e-d14d-435d-bca3-100d6ac490ce",
        "a17e90c4-acc9-4f1d-af84-828ae4cb2289"
      ],
      "settings": {
        "crop": "",
        "image_shape": "default",
        "desktop_media_width": "lg:col-span-7_lg:col-span-5",
        "show_slideshow_arrows_on_desktop": false,
        "enable_image_zoom": false,
        "enable_video_looping": true,
        "autoplay_videos_on_desktop": true,
        "media_mobile_width": "w-full",
        "thumbnails_position": "left",
        "thumbnail_crop": "aspect-w-1 aspect-h-1",
        "thumbnail_shape": "default",
        "hide_media_shadow": false,
        "thumbnail_size": "large",
        "show_thumbnails_on_mobile": false,
        "color_scheme": "tertiary",
        "use_gradient_background": false
      }
    },
    "502b5396-367c-41d7-b6c7-a1f7892bb3c8": {
      "type": "testimonials",
      "disabled": true,
      "blocks": {
        "template--16010042015906__502b5396-367c-41d7-b6c7-a1f7892bb3c8-16684121765ed8f7a4-0": {
          "type": "testimonial",
          "settings": {
            "rating": "5_stars",
            "quote": "<p>A quote from a customer or staff member can help show of your products' unique selling points.<\/p>",
            "source": "Source"
          }
        },
        "template--16010042015906__502b5396-367c-41d7-b6c7-a1f7892bb3c8-16684121765ed8f7a4-1": {
          "type": "testimonial",
          "settings": {
            "rating": "5_stars",
            "quote": "<p>A quote from a customer or staff member can help show of your products' unique selling points.<\/p>",
            "source": "Source"
          }
        },
        "template--16010042015906__502b5396-367c-41d7-b6c7-a1f7892bb3c8-16684121765ed8f7a4-2": {
          "type": "testimonial",
          "settings": {
            "rating": "5_stars",
            "quote": "<p>A quote from a customer or staff member can help show of your products' unique selling points.<\/p>",
            "source": "Source"
          }
        }
      },
      "block_order": [
        "template--16010042015906__502b5396-367c-41d7-b6c7-a1f7892bb3c8-16684121765ed8f7a4-0",
        "template--16010042015906__502b5396-367c-41d7-b6c7-a1f7892bb3c8-16684121765ed8f7a4-1",
        "template--16010042015906__502b5396-367c-41d7-b6c7-a1f7892bb3c8-16684121765ed8f7a4-2"
      ],
      "settings": {
        "display_on_card": true,
        "title": "Customer Reviews",
        "max_width": 100,
        "disable_media_style": false,
        "crop": "",
        "image_shape": "default",
        "desktop_slide_width": 20,
        "autoscroll_mode": "1",
        "color_scheme": "primary",
        "use_gradient_background": false
      }
    },
    "product-recommendations": {
      "type": "product-recommendations",
      "settings": {
        "show_product_recommendations": true,
        "display_on_card": false,
        "enable_quick_buy": false,
        "product_recommendations_heading": "You may also like",
        "max_products": "3",
        "product_tiles_aspect_ratio": "",
        "image_shape": "",
        "color_scheme": "primary",
        "use_gradient_background": false
      }
    },
    "4a1ae5e2-2a30-49d5-bff6-769272b96cd1": {
      "type": "faq",
      "blocks": {
        "template--16010042015906__4a1ae5e2-2a30-49d5-bff6-769272b96cd1-1668414519e48829f5-0": {
          "type": "question",
          "settings": {
            "question": "WHAT IS HYDRATION? ",
            "answer": "<p>Hydration is defined as the process of absorbing water. The human body is roughly 60% water, so hydration is crucial for everything you do daily, especially exercise. Without enough hydration, your body lacks the water levels necessary to function optimally, this is called dehydration.<\/p>"
          }
        },
        "template--16010042015906__4a1ae5e2-2a30-49d5-bff6-769272b96cd1-1668414519e48829f5-1": {
          "type": "question",
          "settings": {
            "question": "WHAT IS PROPER OR OPTIMAL HYDRATION? ",
            "answer": "<p>Athletes should generally be supplementing water with electrolytes both DURING activity as well as throughout the day. Good hydration is always important, but particularly in the days and weeks before an event or after a hard workout. Use GU Hydration Drink Tabs whenever, wherever, and you'll see a boost in preparation, sustenance, as well as recovery.<\/p>"
          }
        },
        "template--16010042015906__4a1ae5e2-2a30-49d5-bff6-769272b96cd1-1668414519e48829f5-2": {
          "type": "question",
          "settings": {
            "question": "HOW DO HYDRATION DRINK TABS WORK? ",
            "answer": "<p>They provide a good balance of fluids and electrolytes. Fluids from water combined with the key electrolyte sodium in our Hydration Drink Tabs help your body hold onto hydration. If you drink water alone, the body will expel it quickly. If you drink water with sodium, the water will hang around longer in your body to help keep you hydrated and prevent dehydration.<\/p>"
          }
        },
        "template--16010042015906__4a1ae5e2-2a30-49d5-bff6-769272b96cd1-1668414519e48829f5-3": {
          "type": "question",
          "settings": {
            "question": "WHY ARE ENERGY GELS MADE WITH TWO TYPES OF CARBOHYDRATES?",
            "answer": "<p>Carbohydrates are efficient energy, and we use a blend of carbs to deliver more energy into the bloodstream as efficiently as possible. Our system of dual-source carbohydrates provides an “express lane” for each carb to deliver energy to your body much quicker than a single source of carbs, which helps you avoid “the bonk” during training and racing.<\/p>"
          }
        },
        "template--16010042015906__4a1ae5e2-2a30-49d5-bff6-769272b96cd1-1668414519e48829f5-4": {
          "type": "question",
          "settings": {
            "question": "WHEN SHOULD I TAKE AN ENERGY GEL?",
            "answer": "<p>We pack 100 calories into our Energy Gels because, in general, the body can digest roughly 120-240 calories per hour during exercise. If you tried to eat more, the body would divert blood from your muscles back to the gut to handle the excess food\/calories. If your metabolism is slower, then one Energy Gel every 45 minutes works just fine. If you have a faster metabolism, try ingesting one Energy Gel every 30 minutes and see if it agrees with your digestion system. We always recommend practicing your nutrition plan to determine what works best for you.<\/p>"
          }
        },
        "template--16010042015906__4a1ae5e2-2a30-49d5-bff6-769272b96cd1-1668414519e48829f5-5": {
          "type": "question",
          "settings": {
            "question": "HOW DO I EAT AN ENERGY GEL? DO I HAVE TO EAT THE ENTIRE ENERGY GEL AT ONE TIME?",
            "answer": "<p>Rip open the top and squeeze the entire packet into your mouth—don’t save half of it for later. It’s also completely appropriate to “sip” the Energy Gel over the course of a couple minutes rather than slamming the it all at once. Our Energy Gels were designed to be taken in one shot to provide you with maximum benefits.<\/p>"
          }
        },
        "template--16010042015906__4a1ae5e2-2a30-49d5-bff6-769272b96cd1-1668414519e48829f5-6": {
          "type": "question",
          "settings": {
            "question": "CAN I USE AN ENERGY GEL FOR A STRENGTH WORKOUT OR YOGA? ",
            "answer": "<p>Sure! While GU Energy Gels were designed for endurance sports, they can be used anytime you need energy to fuel a workout, regardless of what type. Exercise is either aerobic or anaerobic, but you’re burning calories either way.<\/p>"
          }
        },
        "template--16010042015906__4a1ae5e2-2a30-49d5-bff6-769272b96cd1-1668414519e48829f5-7": {
          "type": "question",
          "settings": {
            "question": "HOW DOES THE CAFFEINE IN GU ENERGY GELS HELP ME? ",
            "answer": "<p>GU Energy Gels and ROCTANE Energy Gels come in both caffeinated and non-caffeinated flavors. Caffeine is more than just a morning pick-me-up. Strategically adding caffeine to your nutrition plan before and during exercise can help keep your mind sharp, decrease perceived effort, boost your endurance, and delay fatigue<\/p>"
          }
        },
        "27f762fc-c580-4269-b289-da9d334708a4": {
          "type": "question",
          "settings": {
            "question": "DO GU ENERGY GELS FREEZE?",
            "answer": "<p>Yes, but well below zero. They will thicken in cold weather, so keep your Energy Gels close to your body to keep it warm.<\/p>"
          }
        },
        "48a3ab3a-938b-447c-bbdd-54e70c1be370": {
          "type": "question",
          "settings": {
            "question": "HOW LONG DOES AN ENERGY GEL TAKE TO WORK?",
            "answer": "<p>Right away! The fructose converts quickly into an energy molecule that your muscles can tap within minutes. The maltodextrin, which makes up 70-80% of the carbohydrate blend (depending on flavor), takes several minutes longer. Because of this delay, your muscles enjoy a steady stream of energy instead of one gigantic sugar rush and a corresponding crash.<\/p>"
          }
        },
        "2ac8f77b-14da-4c16-87af-6c69d87d2dda": {
          "type": "question",
          "settings": {
            "question": "ARE ENERGY GELS SAFE FOR CHILDREN? ",
            "answer": "<p>Yes, if they’re playing sports, on a hike, or active, GU Energy Gels can help kids just as much as they help you. You may want to keep them away from flavors that contain caffeine, though.<\/p>"
          }
        },
        "21860d85-a529-4c2f-a455-7ecb43a377ae": {
          "type": "question",
          "settings": {
            "question": "ARE GU ENERGY GELS KOSHER, VEGAN-FRIENDLY AND GLUTEN-FREE?",
            "answer": "<p>GU Energy Gels and ROCTANE Energy Gels are both kosher certified, gluten-free and vegan-friendly.<\/p>"
          }
        }
      },
      "block_order": [
        "template--16010042015906__4a1ae5e2-2a30-49d5-bff6-769272b96cd1-1668414519e48829f5-0",
        "template--16010042015906__4a1ae5e2-2a30-49d5-bff6-769272b96cd1-1668414519e48829f5-1",
        "template--16010042015906__4a1ae5e2-2a30-49d5-bff6-769272b96cd1-1668414519e48829f5-2",
        "template--16010042015906__4a1ae5e2-2a30-49d5-bff6-769272b96cd1-1668414519e48829f5-3",
        "template--16010042015906__4a1ae5e2-2a30-49d5-bff6-769272b96cd1-1668414519e48829f5-4",
        "template--16010042015906__4a1ae5e2-2a30-49d5-bff6-769272b96cd1-1668414519e48829f5-5",
        "template--16010042015906__4a1ae5e2-2a30-49d5-bff6-769272b96cd1-1668414519e48829f5-6",
        "template--16010042015906__4a1ae5e2-2a30-49d5-bff6-769272b96cd1-1668414519e48829f5-7",
        "27f762fc-c580-4269-b289-da9d334708a4",
        "48a3ab3a-938b-447c-bbdd-54e70c1be370",
        "2ac8f77b-14da-4c16-87af-6c69d87d2dda",
        "21860d85-a529-4c2f-a455-7ecb43a377ae"
      ],
      "settings": {
        "display_on_card": true,
        "heading_text_style": "body",
        "two_columns_desktop": true,
        "title": "FAQ",
        "richtext": "<p>Find the most frequently asked questions below.<\/p>",
        "color_scheme": "tertiary",
        "use_gradient_background": false
      }
    },
    "181d154b-8a7e-4535-b502-4962d48547f0": {
      "type": "geldiscription",
      "blocks": {
        "938cd65f-2d68-4ca6-87a0-0db0492e8c01": {
          "type": "title",
          "settings": {
            "roctin": "Pop, Drop, & GO."
          }
        },
        "4645f6d5-e730-4dde-8a61-3b8885de78be": {
          "type": "discription",
          "settings": {
            "discript": "GU Hydration Drink Tabs are designed to keep you hydrated during any activity and in all conditions. Tablets are easily dissolved in 16 ounces of water, perfect for dropping into a sport bottle or bike bottle for hydration on-the-go. The light, effervescent tablets are also appropriate for everyday use, during training, travel, and hot weather, or anytime you need a hydration boost. The 12-tablet portable tubes easily fit in pockets, jerseys, and running belts. All flavors are caffeine-free and made with vegan ingredients."
          }
        }
      },
      "block_order": [
        "938cd65f-2d68-4ca6-87a0-0db0492e8c01",
        "4645f6d5-e730-4dde-8a61-3b8885de78be"
      ],
      "settings": {
        "gel": "GU HYDRATION DRINK TABS"
      }
    }
  },
  "order": [
    "main",
    "502b5396-367c-41d7-b6c7-a1f7892bb3c8",
    "product-recommendations",
    "4a1ae5e2-2a30-49d5-bff6-769272b96cd1",
    "181d154b-8a7e-4535-b502-4962d48547f0"
  ]
}
